One classroom. Every voice. One Trek.
Do not watch a slideshow.
Watch one class shape where the lesson goes next.
Open Trek Exchange.
Discover reviewed Treks, ranked and shared by the community.
Remix any Trek for your class.
Student-made Treks require teacher approval.
Now Nova joins from a student device.
Nova reacts, votes for liquid water, and explains:
ice is useful only if the crew also has energy.
The teacher's live pulse changes as the response arrives.
The room becomes one readable view.
The teacher can share a safe idea anonymously,
without exposing the student's identity.
Mission Control asks ClassTrek
to read the room.
GPT-5.6 combines de-identified reasoning
with sources selected for this Trek.
The proposal cannot publish itself.
The teacher checks the evidence and decides.
Approve and publish.
One click advances the canonical lesson version.
Every connected screen moves to the same next question.
Students contribute evidence. AI proposes a branch.
Software enforces safety. The teacher remains in control.
Every response passes classroom guardrails.
Unsafe text never reaches the public display.
Codex accelerated realtime state, recovery, structured GPT output,
safety tests, and real multi-browser verification.
Little steps become one big learning journey.
Together.